plan3d.com 2008-06-16

# 

**Licensee of TRUSTe Privacy Program**  
Plan3D is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.  TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  This privacy statement covers the site www.plan3D.com.  Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.plan3D.com&sealid=101)If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Michael Gariepy at support@plan3D.com.  If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at [TRUSTe WATCHDOG LINK](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php).  TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from this site.

**The Information We Collect**  
At this site, you can order products, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected includes: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about some hardware on your computer.

We may collect certain personally identifiable information when you visit our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '95 or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink) and information about your hardware settings (e.g., the type of 3D video card, CPU speed, amount of memory and so on) to provide you with technical support and to allow plan3D to operate correctly on your computer.

REGISTRATION: In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password.  During registration you are also required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.   This information may be used to send you information about your membership such as newsletters, upgrade information, renewal notices, etc. 

ORDERS: If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders.  If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

**Owner of Information Collected**  
Plan3D, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on the plan3D website. Plan3D collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**How We Use the Information**  
We may use information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you - although we will never give your information to other people or companies outside plan3D without your explicit permission.

We may use this information to communicate with you, when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.

We sometimes use the personally identifiable information that we collect about your computer hardware to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience and to provide technical support. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services from time to time.

Employees and contractors of Plan3D who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Plan3D.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.

Finally, Plan3D sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name.  We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Your Personal Information Shared with Order-Processing Companies:  **We use other third parties to provide online order processing __on our site.   When you sign up for plan3D, we will share your name, address and credit card information with Verisign corporation and E-Merchants Bank __as necessary for them to process the credit card order so we can provide the plan3D service to you.

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose than to confirm that you are authorized to use the credit card, process the financial transaction for plan3D. 

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**  
Plan3D sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. Plan3D has no control over the third-party sponsors' use of this information. Plan3D will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third-party sponsors will obtain such information.

**Cookies**  
To enhance your experience at Plan3D, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

**Security** **Practices**   
The security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at support@plan3D.com 

**Effective Date and Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
These privacy policies were updated on March 31st, 2006 to meet TRUSTe requirements. They were also approved by TRUSTe on March 31st, 2006.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

**How You Can Access or Correct Information**  
For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that Plan3D has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please contact us.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update or delete it by making the change on our member information page (under My Account) or by emailing support@plan3D.com or by contacting us through postal mail at the contact information listed below.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Opting Out of Communications**  
We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.  For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. 

You may not opt out of receiving information from us directly related to your subscription such as an activation email, refund notice, changes in your membership status emails or emails informing you about renewing. 

To receive the plan3D newsletter email from us you must put a checkmark in the box next to "Send me the plan3D newsletter" under the "My Account" link on www.plan3D.com - after you log in as a member. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, you may opt-out of receiving it by emailing us at support@plan3d.com with that request. You may also opt out of receiving communications from us by contacting us customerService@plan3D.com or by sending a letter t 8549 E. Tanque Verde, Tucson, AZ 85749.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about the Plan3D online privacy policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at:

> Business Email:  
> 
> Business Address:  
>  Michael Gariepy  
>  President   
>  Plan3D, Inc.  
>  8549 E. Tanque Verde  
>  Tucson, AZ 85749
